Jade. I need you
to start on the bathrooms.
Joslyn. can you please
take out all the eggs. batter.
patties and McMuffins
out of the freezer. okay?
I'll help you once I turn everything on.
Good morning. team.
No. no. no.
Don't be scared.
You just do what I say.
no one gets hurt. okay?
No. no. look.
Pointing it down.
Okay. now. I'm gonna say a polite
and cheerful "Good morning."
and then you guys say it back.
Good morning.
No... Duane. after I say it.
That's how that works. Okay?
Now. good morning. team.
Good morning.
Yes. Perfect.
I say what to do
and you guys just do it. Okay.
I want you to get your coats back on.
Duane. grab your coat.
- Huh?
- Grab your coat.
I don't have one. sir.
You don't have a coat?
How do you not have a coat?
I just forgot.
Well. you're just gonna
have to be a little cold today.
All right. let's go.
After you. Ladies first.
Now. listen to me.
You guys aren't gonna die in here.
Soon as I'm out of here.
I'm gonna call the cops
and they're gonna let you guys out.
Probably get the day off.
No. don't. don't.
Do not look at me like that.
Duane. stop it.
'Cause this is your fault.
- It's cold.
- Are you serious?
Dang it.
I don't know what kind of jerk
doesn't bring his own coat to work.
Okay? Happy now?
My ears are cold.
This is the part of the story
where I hope you're wondering
how a nice guy like me
ends up becoming a criminal.
Hello?
This thing on?
Shit!
Come on. Duane.
Good morning. Uh. welcome to McDonald's.
I'm gonna put you on a brief hold.
What the hell. Duane?
I can't blame my parents.
I had a good childhood.
I was just never good
at school or behaving.
But I was good at certain things
that were really valuable to the military.
But after my discharge.
I didn't know where I fit or what to do
or how to give my kids
the things that other kids had.
So I made some bad choices
that took away some other choices.
And those bad choices
all started two years ago
at my daughter's sixth birthday party.
All right.
you got to make a big ol' wish.
One more.
Did you make a wish? What'd you wish for?
- A bike.
- Bike?
I don't know if a bike
is exactly gonna fit
into this box. but... rip it open.
I'm gonna race ya. Yeah.
What do you think?
It's cool. right? It's my old Erector Set.
Let's open it up.
There's 200 pieces in here.
No!
I mean. you got engines.
you got gears. pulleys.
wheels. lights. switches.
We can make almost anything
that we want with this thing.
Look. anything that you can dream.
we can make it. okay?
Me and you. What do you say?
Can you make a bike with it?
Yeah.
I can't believe the dude I knew
from the 82nd can't even afford a bike.
Well. tell me how you're doing so well.
Well. let me see.
Just this week. I got
two Japanese dudes passports.
That's 5K a pop.
Five grand for fake passports?
- No. for real passports.
- Man...
Can I help you with that?
Hell motherfucking no. you can't.
You can't help me with shit.
You crazy. man?
You ain't helping me do a goddamn thing.
I don't need your help.
Plus. we already know
that doing things the right way
is not your superpower.
Whatever. That's...
Okay. then tell me
what my superpower is. then?
- Enlighten me. Buddha.
- Mm.
What's the flow rate on that hose?
- 12 gallons per minute.
- Mm-hmm.
How many houses is on this street?
Twenty-eight.
And out of those. how many got chimneys?
Garages?
How many of 'em use a heat pump
instead of a traditional AC?
You want me to sell HVAC systems
or something? Just...
No. no. man. I'm trying to make a point.
Then make the point. please.
Observation.
Details.
You see shit people don't see.
You got like
a little X-ray vision going on.
What. you think they dropped you off
in Central America 'cause you a good shot?
- Is that what you think?
- No. No...
No. they dropped you
because of what you see.
Shit. if I had a brain like yours.
I'd be running the whole goddamn world.
You know. you the smartest
dumb nigga I ever known.
That shit crazy.
You can stop filling up that pool now.
Ain't nobody gonna get in there.
That shit cold as hell.
So. Mama
is probably gonna want to know
how the party was.
and. yeah. I think we did our best.
What do you think?
Maybe we don't mention the pool.
It's the trying that counts. right?
Mommy!
Hi. birthday girl.
How was your party?
Everybody did their best.
Oh. Are you ready
for your other party?
Hi.
How are you?
Hey. can I talk to you for a second?
Real-real quick. real quick.
I know the last few months
haven't been easy.
and we don't have the things
that we actually need.
and that's my fault and I own that.
Okay? I do. but I-I think
I have it figured out now.
I just got to use my superpower and
- put my brain on what I want.
- Your superpower?
- Yes.
- I can't do this. Jeff.
- Look-- No.
- I'm done.
- Come on. please don't do this.
Goodbye.
All right. banana head.
Say goodbye.
Love you!
Wait. wait. wait. wait. wait. wait!
I didn't blame her
for laughing at me.
For thinking I was a joke.
But there were things
that she didn't know about me.
Things that weren't so funny.
Steve knew what I was capable of.
I do see things
that other people don't see.
Like right now. I see that kid
climbing up that ladder.
and I know that under that flimsy roof
is a machine that turns ground beef
and potatoes into money.
With the same dining room.
the same deep fryers
with blinking red timer lights.
the same shake machine
with the same two flavors
and the same safe full of
weekend corporate burger money
that no one was gonna miss.
They empty that safe
at the exact same time
on Monday morning
at every single McDonald's.
Hi. Welcome to McDonald's.
Do you know what you want?
Huh?
Yeah. Yeah. yeah. yeah.
Um. yeah. I figured it out.
Thank you.
There are over 10.000
almost identical McDonald's
across the United States.
Question was: How many do you need to rob
to get a real house.
buy your kids nice things
and win your family back?
Turns out. the answer is 45.
The Roof man has struck again.
cutting a hole through the roof
of this McDonald's
at the corner of Madison
and Jewell in Fayetteville.
As you can imagine.
this was a terrifying experience.
He came in.
threw us in the freezer
and gave me his coat.
-He gave you his coat?
- Yes.
Uh. yeah. he didn't want me to be cold.
He was actually really nice.
Police believe
this is the same suspect
who has been terrorizing
our local community
with 45 incidents...
- Mm.
- ...this pasty ear alone.
We have a sketch of the Roof man.
He is always wearing a mask.
He's described as six-foot-two
with an athletic build.
- What?
- The Roof man has also struck
Burger King. Kentucky Fried Chicken...
Nice TV you got here. Jeff.
Big.
How you afford something like that?
We got 15 hungry kids out there
that are losing their minds for cake.
We got to go.
...all of these brazen incidents...
- We got to go.
- Hold on. hold on.
- We got to go right now.
- Let me see...
If she doesn't get her presents right now...
I want to know what's going on
with the damn suspect.
- ...she's gonna lose her mind.
- Can I see?
- All right.
- Why you turning it off?
Wait. wait. wait. wait. wait. wait.
Don't. don't. don't. d--
Come on.
Let's go.
Goddamn. man.
♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
♪ Happy birthday ♪
♪ To you ♪
♪ Happy birthday. bandida ♪
- ♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
- You.
Let's go!
All right.
Big breath. big wish. Here we go.
All right. we're gonna do
this one first this year.
Big things in little boxes.
What is this?
A garage door opener?
Why'd you give me a garage door opener?
I don't know. I just couldn't think
of anywhere else
to put. uh. the saber-toothed tiger. so...
I don't know. I couldn't put it
in the kitchen. could I?
So. where is it?
You're the best daddy
in the whole entire world!
Now. go ahead. get on it.
I love it.
How you guys doing?
We're looking for Jeffrey Manchester.
This about the registration?
Yeah. I got it right in here. One second.
Stop.
You're under arrest!
Whoa! Hey. hey. hey.
Freeze! You're under arrest!
Subtitle
www.movieddl.me
Mr. Manchester. please rise.
The State has proved
beyond the defined burden
that you committed the crime of robbery
with a dangerous weapon.
I'd like to take in consideration
your service to this country
in the armed forces
and the impact of your children
losing a father.
Now. I know you got everyone fooled
thinking you're a nice guy.
but I know you're a menace.
Although you're only
being tried for one robbery.
we know you've done many more.
And so the prosecution has requested
that I issue a single count
of felony kidnapping
for each victim you locked in the freezer.
Let the record state that
on the 4th of February. 2004.
you're hereby sentenced to 180 months
for each of the three victims.
for a total of 540 months or 45 years
in the North Carolina
Department of Corrections.
Mr. Sheriff. he is in your custody.
This concludes this case.
Hi. Daddy.
I really missed you.
Miss you. too. I miss you a lot.
Hey. did you get the letter
that I drew the big ol' house on it?
No.
Well. maybe it hasn't arrived. Ask Mama.
Mom says she'll save the letters.
When I'm old enough. I can read them.
No. no. That is not... that is not right.
These letters are for.
they're for right now.
Tell him we're cutting the cord.
They said we have to cut the cord.
No. we're not cutting the cord.
Who said that?
We went to a meeting
for families with dads in prison.
Okay. well. that's good.
That's really good. What'd they say there?
That it isn't my fault. It's your fault.
And to let you go. all the way.
'cause you'll never come home.
even if you say you will.
Look. that last part is not--
that is very. very wrong.
You have 60 seconds remaining.
Hey. can you put your mom on for a second?
He wants to talk to you.
No. Tell him that you have to hang up.
Gary's gonna help you with your homework.
She doesn't want to talk to you.
She said I have to get off
and do homework.
Gary is going to help me.
Gary? Who's Gary?
Mom's friend.
Huh. Mom's got a new friend named Gary.
That's-that's fun.
It's okay. sweetheart.
You can tell him.
Um. okay. I'm gonna call you
tomorrow at the same time
I always do. all right?
They said no more calls.
No. no. Who said that? No.
Hang up the phone.
It's okay. Becky.
- You can hang up now.
- Hang up?
Is that Gary?
Put him on the phone right now.
Hang up. Hang up.
Put Gary or your mom
on the phone right now. Becky. okay?
- I have to hang up.
- Hey.
Listen to me. I'm coming home.
Tell your brothers I'm coming home.
And we don't say goodbye.
'cause goodbye means going away
and going away means
forgetting. and we're...
We're-- H-Hello?
Hello?
B... Becky?
Why is you
still thinking about them?
You got to let that go.
Ain't no getting out of here.
Get that idea out your head.
Every prisoner
wants the same thing:
to get out of prison.
And they think that the way out
is through a wall
or over a fence.
But the guards got that covered.
The way out of prison
is through the people.
Prison was just another building
full of systems and routines.
Keep the routine.
and the guards won't get suspicious.
If you're nice enough. if you're useful.
they forget you're in there for a reason.
And when they stop watching you.
you can start watching them.
You smell that?
Smells like you're leaking.
How 'bout checking it out for me.
- Yes. sir.
- See if you see anything.
Yeah.
Doesn't look too bad just yet.
I don't know-- it'll probably get you
back to where you're going.
- All right. Well. come on out of there.
- All right.
Yeah. you better
tell your maintenance guy.
You might need a new gasket.
- I appreciate it. man.
- Yes. sir.
- Have a good one.
- You. too.
Yeah. Straight back.
- Two boxes.
- Yep.
- Two benches.
- Yes. sir.
All right.
Shut her down.
- She's all yours. Mr. Cummings.
- Thank you. bud.
Hey. smells like you fixed it.
Good catch.
- All right. drive safe.
- All right. have a good one.
Jesus.
Phew.
Yeah.
Yeah. pedal. pedal. pedal. pedal. pedal.
Hello?
Steve. It's me.
Jeff. Jeff. what the fuck
are you doing calling me. man?
You all over the goddamn news and shit.
Look. I got to get out of the country.
I'm thinking. like. Brazil or Venezuela.
Somewhere with a beach and no extradition.
God. you sound fucking crazy.
I know. I'm sorry.
Don't do no stupid shit
like go see your family.
- Hide. All right?
- Okay. Okay. I'll hide.
Don't call back for another month.
All right. I'm-a call you in a month.
And don't call
my motherfucking phone again.
You got it? A'ight.
Steve?
St--
- You.
- A lot.
A lot? We have-- Yep.
What do you want?
- A monkey.
- A monkey?
Wait a minute.
- Turtle.
- What-- and what do you want?
- Candy.
Candy?
We got a lot of candy.
Uh. um. sir. we're closing here
in ten minutes.
- Sir?
- Yeah. no problem.
I got you.
Zero. three. six.
five. nine. eight. two.
Bathroom's clear.
Attention. Toys "R" Us customers.
Our store will be closing in five minutes.
So. if you are not a toy or an employee.
please bring your purchases
up to the front.
Whether you are a kid or a parent
or an uncle or a friend
making a dream come true.
it is time to make your choices
and meet us at the register up front.
If you can't decide tonight. don't worry.
We promise you we will be here tomorrow.
just as long as you promise us
to never grow up.
Jeffrey Manchester.
also known as the Roof man.
escaped from Brown Creek Prison
earlier today.
Tonight. he's still out there somewhere.
Authorities discovered Manchester.
who was serving 45 years
for armed robbery and kidnapping.
was missing this afternoon...
- Ha.
- ...during a routine head count.
Correction officers do not know the method
or exact time of Manchester's escape...
They still don't know how I got out.
...but believe he may still be
in the Charlotte area.
- No. no. no. I'm-I'm long gone.
- We believe he fled
sometime between 12:00 and 4:00
this afternoon.
He's a very smart individual.
Super intelligent.
Probably genius level.
But he's also an absolute idiot.
We believe that the suspect
could be armed.
And he has a history of violent behavior.
- What?
- Police are asking
if you see someone
who looks like Manchester.
please call authorities
and do not confront him.
Okay.
All right.
Yeah.
Password:
one. two. three. four. five. six.
Whoa. Yeah.
Most guys. when they escape.
get caught in the first few hours.
They go as far as they can
as fast as they can.
And that never works.
The trick is to stop.
Find a place no one will look.
Sometimes.
the best hiding places are in plain sight.
A place where people
are too preoccupied to see you.
So I kept quiet as a mouse.
But not at night.
I owned the night.
♪ Where did we go wrong? ♪
The manhunt for the Roof man
enters its third day.
People
have short attention spans.
After a while. they get bored.
I figured I had to be quiet
for about a month. give or take.
Still no leads from police
on the whereabouts
of escaped convict Jeffrey Manchester.
as the manhunt enters its eighth day.
One time.
when I was in the 82nd.
I spent 30 days in the woods
surviving off of rain water and grubs.
Your body doesn't need much to keep going.
It's your brain
that you have to take care of.
If you can make your brain
imagine a better place.
it can get you through anything.
Just pick any place but where you are.
Like a beach on an ocean.
A place where your kids can visit
after everyone else forgets you.
Nearly two weeks
since Jeffrey Manchester escaped
from Brown Creek Penitentiary.
Police have set up roadblocks.
concerned Manchester
may still be in the area.
Sergeant. I'm with Channel 6 News.
Jeffrey Manchester's still missing.
Do you think he could be in Charlotte?
He might've kept moving.
but we're not gonna give up
on the possibility
that he still might be hiding out here
in Mecklenburg County.
And when he tries to run. we'll be ready.
Good luck.
♪ Never trust another♪
♪ 'Cause they're all out to getcha ♪
♪ We have to live in this world together♪
♪ 'Gether♪
♪ if we open up our heart
Love can finally start ♪
♪ Come on and try ♪
♪ Now's the time ♪
♪ 'Cause you're free ♪
♪ To do what you want to do ♪
♪ You got to live your life ♪
♪ Do what you want to do ♪
♪ Do what you want ♪
One quick question.
Uh. yeah.
Okay. I just wanted
to talk to you about my hours.
Um...
I need every other weekend off.
I'm confused.
First you ask me for a job.
and now you're asking me for time off.
Well. you know.
- I'm a team player...
- Yeah.
...but. um. I'm also a mom.
I know.
- Okay. Well...
- I do.
- Uh...
- You-you reminded me.
I got a divorce six months ago. so...
it's really hard for me to
balance everything right now
with work and my girls and my ex.
- Oh. come on.
- The custody situation is:
They have. you know.
one weekend him. one weekend me.
I don't want to bore you
with my personal problems.
Good. good. 'Cause I don't want to be
bored by your personal problems.
If this is a Toys "R" Us problem.
then I'm interested.
But personal problems
belong on personal time.
Thank you. Leigh.
Got to get back to payroll.
Work. work. work. work. work. work. work.
Good to see you.
- What a dick.
- Thanks. Mitch.
Okay.
Unbelievable.
Yeah. you're an unbelievable dick.
I know you're a mom.
You mentioned it before.
Mom card. Unbelievable.
Dollar sign. U.
C. C. E.
dollar sign. dollar sign.
That's the dumbest password
I've ever... I've ever heard of.
"$ucce$$."
Heh.
We found Leigh.
Saturday.
Goodbye.
Boop. boop. boop. boop. boop.
boop. boop. boop. boop. boop.
You have the day off now.
Voilà.
The news starts now.
More than 30.000 folks
are expected to crowd into town.
...came up with
the idea "Babe Wash."
And the bikinis do bring in the business.
The biggest
celebrations of the Fourth
take place in the skies right behind me.
People get bored
with last week's news.
Pretty soon. they can't even remember
why they know your face.
Even cops lose interest
unless you really piss 'em off.
Everybody forgets you eventually.
Except people who really love you.
I couldn't get to the people
who love me now without hurting them.
The only place I might ever see them again
was somewhere else and some other time.
The first step was getting out of here...
...to get there.
Hello?
Hi. Um...
Wh-- Is. uh-- May I. may I speak to Steve?
- Please?
- Sorry. who is this?
Oh. this is a friend.
Well. I mean. this is... Oliver.
His. uh. his cousin.
I was-- I'm doing this little...
little cross-country trip. and. uh.
he was. he was expecting me.
I was supposed to visit.
Mm. Mm.
He didn't say anything about a visit.
And I didn't know he had a cousin.
He must have forgot to mention it.
I guess.
Um...
Who am I sp-- who am I speaking with?
Oh. I'm his girlfriend.
What is this about. though?
'Cause I'm in the middle
of something. so. uh...
His girl-- okay. great.
Could I talk to Steve now?
He isn't here.
Okay. well.
should I call back in. like. a...
like. an hour or so?
Uh. well. he's not gonna be back
until December 1st.
Where does anyone go till December?
He's in Afghanistan.
He's not in Afghanistan.
We got back two years ago
from Afghanistan.
Well. he took a six-month contract.
Um. but he asked me
to take messages for him.
Is there something that you want me
to tell him if he calls?
Yeah. uh...
tell him that. uh.
Cousin Oliver is gonna stay
with relatives in the area until he's back
on December 1st
for a really important meeting.
Okay. I will tell him that.
And. uh. I will see you then. too.
I guess.
Cousin Oliver.
Bye.
Hello?
Stop tickling me. Just a sec.
Gary is crazy.
Gary!
Who is it? Hello?
- Hello?
- Gary.
Who is this?
Jeff. is this you?
If you call here again.
I'm gonna call the cops.
Do you hear me?
We've moved on.
And you need to move on. too.
Don't call here anymore.
That tickles.
Oh. boy. that tickles.
Elmo wants to play.
Let's play.
Oh. boy. that tickles.
Elmo loves you.
-Elmo wants to play.
- You're Elmo's sweetheart.
-That tickles.
- Let's play.
Elmo loves you.
Oh. boy. that tickles.
Let's play.
Elmo loves you.
♪ Elmo loves his ABCs... ♪
- Hey. Leigh.
- Otee-Otee-Otis.
Hey.
Hey. Mitch.
You're just the man I want to see.
Cool.
You. uh...
you like Peanut M&Ms. right?
- Yeah.
- Yeah?
Yeah.
'Cause we're missing a lot of Peanut M&Ms.
-You have any idea why?
- No.
- What's wrong?
- Nothing's wrong.
- Seem nervous.
- I'm not.
No.
- No?
- No. Not happening.
You can't talk to him like that.
Okay. You know. we are missing
half a dozen boxes out there.
And I just thought-- boop--
they got to be hiding somewhere-- boop.
I am so sorry.
- Oh. God.
- He cannot talk to you that way.
I'm the bad guy now.
Hey. You got to
stick up for yourself.
Okay? Or he's just gonna get worse.
I'm not big on conflict. so...
- Yeah.
- Okay. well. we'll-we'll work on that.
Cool.
Listen. Mitch.
you really hurt Otis's feelings.
and I think you should apologize.
I'm sorry.
Well. that's a good start.
- Okay.
- You know.
people respect kindness in a leader.
Mm.
W-With that in mind.
I wanted to invite you to my church.
Crossroads Church.
It's. uh. just across the interstate.
- Uh...
- Have you been?
Not very churchy.
Okay. well. I'm in charge
of the toy drive there.
and it got me thinking. here I am.
working in a toy store of all places.
and you haven't even donated
one toy to my toy drive.
Well. we sell toys here.
We don't give 'em away.
Okay. What about all those returned toys?
Perfectly good ones that we can't sell.
We run a business here. Leigh.
Okay. Well. you can still come.
You know. all people are welcome.
Even if they're mean
or aren't quite ready yet.
So you can come.
bring a big bag of toys. or not.
You'll be welcome.
But bring the toys
and you could be a good guy for once.
Don't you want to be a good guy?
Come on. Mitch! Be a good guy!
Okay.
Is that garbage?
Uh...
Huh?
Do you want me to put that
in the garbage for you?
It's just toys for the...
Uh. I heard there was a toy drive.
Well. it's right this way.
It's o-- I'll just leave 'em here.
It's okay.
I'm not gonna walk
all the way down there in these heels.
It's very nice of you.
Here you go.
Thank you.
Oh. it's too heavy for me.
Got to bring it on in there.
Come on. I'll show you where the toys go.
- Where do you want me to put 'em?
- You can bring 'em right in here.
Service is about to begin.
Anyone that feels alone out there...
...just come on down here.
'Cause you belong here.
We're all sinners here.
which is why I ask my wife
sometimes to sing this tune.
♪ In times of despair♪
♪ I think about the good things
That you've done ♪
♪ Ooh. and though you're not there ♪
♪ I sometimes ask myself♪
- ♪ Is anyone? ♪
- ♪ Yeah ♪
- ♪ Oh ♪
♪ It's so hard being human ♪
♪ With all the troubles ♪
♪ In sight ♪
♪ But somehow I know ♪
♪ I know. I know. I know. I know ♪
♪ Everything's gonna work out all right ♪
♪ Hey. yeah ♪
♪ But somehow I know ♪
♪ Everything's gonna work out all right ♪
♪ Hey. but somehow I know ♪
Hallelujah.
Wow. Somebody is very hungry. huh?
Big appetite there. huh?
- Sorry.
- Please.
I haven't had food this good
in so long.
No. that's great. Big food for a big guy.
- Yeah.
Now. you can't sneak out of here
without saying hello
to the pastor and his wife.
- No.
- It's against the rules.
No. I would never. I would never.
I'm Eileen.
John. Z-- uh. Zorin. John Zorin.
Yeah. I haven't seen you
around the area before.
I noticed you. obviously.
in the. in the-the row there.
Where are you from? You new to the area?
Yeah. uh. I'm-I'm...
I'm just new to this place
and. really. everything.
You know. it's. um...
All of this is really just. you know...
Every-Everything here is just new for me.
I'm-I'm down from New York City.
That's a walking man's town.
I mean. if ever I've been-been to one.
- That is a walking man's town.
- That is correct.
I bet you go through a lot
of pair of sneakers. don't you?
- Everyone does.
- Right? Do you go through...
- Yeah. yeah.
- Oh. my. You've--
You got very small feet for a big guy.
No. I actually have large feet. It's just.
I put on the wrong shoes.
and I don't know.
I think these are. like. nines in women's.
And I'm sorry. I would never
wear sneakers to church.
I-I'm really sorry.
You know. I-I would like
to introduce you to someone.
I'd like to introduce you
to Leigh Wainscott.
She runs the toy drive here.
and I heard you gave
such a generous donation.
I know she'd like to thank you for it.
You know. she looks a bit busy
over there. actually. Eileen.
She's having a serious conversation
with her daughter.
Now?
- Yeah.
- We can.
- Yeah. Okay.
- You made such a great donation.
- Okay. Yeah. sure.
- Yeah. Hey. hey.
- Okay. great.
- Uh. Leigh. Hey. Leigh.
Leigh. Hey. Leigh.
Come. come say hi to our mystery man.
- Okay.
- Come on.
- Yeah.
This is our all-star Leigh.
She is the backbone of everything
that is good going on in this church.
She does the outreach. does the meals.
does the toy drive. she...
I really don't know how
she does it all. but she does.
And this is John...
Zorin? Zorin from New York.
Oh. New York.
- That's far from here.
- Yeah. a little bit. yeah.
So. John-- he made
a very generous toy donation.
Oh. that's so kind of you. We...
Couldn't have come at a better time.
No. I-I mean. um. I really like Christmas
and-and birthdays.
uh. and just gift-giving time.
I mean. I don't know.
- I just love kids.
- You have kids. John?
- Well...
- You have a family. or are you single?
I'm. uh. just officially
divorced. that's all.
Oh. I'm sorry. John.
- Not-not all marriages work out. right?
- That's-- that is true.
But to answer your question.
I do have kids.
I have two little monster boys.
and I got a little girl
that is my best pal.
- That's sweet.
- And. um... Yeah.
But they're in New York.
and I'm here working.
And what-what-what do you--
what do you do for work?
Well. I...
I-I work for the government.
um. but I can't exactly talk about it.
It's. uh. it's classified
- and all that silliness.
- Oh.
Well. John Zorin from New York.
our New York spy.
No! No. no.
- Definitely not that.
- I like that.
Okay. okay.
Well. can I ask you. can we count on you
to join us next Sunday?
- Yeah.
- Well. and also this Wednesday.
- Oh. Wow. Yeah.
- What's-what's Wednesday?
Uh. I run a singles dinner.
and this week's gonna be at a Red Lobster.
I love a Red Lobster.
I mean. not just the seafood.
Those cheese biscuits...
- Mm-hmm.
- I mean. yeah.
I-I mean. are you gonna be there?
Hmm. Leigh?
You think you're gonna join us
for our first single dinner?
Well. I never thought of myself
as being a single.
but. sure. yeah. I-I'll-I'll go.
- Okay.
- Yeah. I'll-I'll be there.
- Count me in.
- Okay.
- Good to see you.
- Thank you so much.
Thank you for joining us today.
Really appreciate it.
I liked being John
better than I liked being Jeff.
- See you on Wednesday.
- Wednesday. Yes. ma'am.
John was a good guy. People liked him.
Leigh seemed to like him. too.
But there was no way a girl like her
was gonna really fall
for a guy in women's running shoes
and a Spider-Man T-shirt.
Also. I really needed to see a dentist.
Living on candy is hard on your teeth.
- Good afternoon.
- How are you?
Good. sir. How are you?
See what you give me for these.
Uh. how about ten apiece? 300.
Yeah. I'll go 300.
- Okay. let's do that.
- Yeah. deal. Yes. sir.
M.O.D. on number 29.
14 cavities.
That's a lot of cavities for an adult.
Yeah. I'm sorry.
I just have a bit-- naturally. I guess.
a bit of a sweet tooth.
and I've had access
to a lot of really good candy.
- Just haven't been able to...
- Open your mouth
- wide. please.
- ...s-stop. Okay.
Look at those.
Oh. wow.
Hello.
- Hello. ladies.
- Hi!
- Hi.
- How is everyone?
- Good.
Oh. okay.
I thought this was a singles brunch.
not a supermodel brunch.
Ooh.
You could always
squeeze in down here by us.
Well. we wanted to welcome you. John.
- Yes.
- Welcome. welcome.
Am I the only guy
that's gonna be here today?
- Yes.
- Uh-huh. Yep. You are.
- Turns out to be so. yes.
- Right. Okay.
Yes. I hope we're not
overwhelming for you.
Oh. no. no. no. I'm actually--
I-I'm liking it very much.
- Okay. good.
- I love having so many new friends.
especially beautiful friends. Um...
- Ooh.
- Sweet one.
So. John. I understand you work for
the government. What kind of work?
I-I would love to get into those details.
but I'm undercover. so. um...
Oh. that sounds mysterious.
No. I can promise
it's not that mysterious.
It's really quite boring.
I never knew there was
an intelligence unit here in Charlotte.
Oh. are you law enforcement?
I'm retired now. but I was.
Wow. That's amazing.
Am I. am I. uh...
Am I arrested? How does this work?
I don't want to make you upset.
You're embarrassing
everyone. Sally.
He did not come here to be interrogated.
No. no. no. I actually really like it.
I feel a lot safer with her here.
Um. but-but yeah.
Um. there's intelligence
just about in every major city.
We just don't advertise that much. yeah.
Well. if he's undercover. why's he
at a singles dinner at Red Lobster?
That's a fair question.
Well...
- That's a fair question.
- I-I can...
That is. that is a question
that is not classified.
I am here possibly looking
for the next Ms. John Zorin.
Oh. please. Oh. please.
See. but there-there is a problem. though.
I'm having a bit of an issue that there's
just too many beautiful choices here
to choose from.
No. I'm-I'm sorry.
I should not have said that.
My mom always told me
do not compliment a woman
on her beauty because
it makes her self-conscious.
Um. always start with their shoes.
Speaking of. Hold on a second.
Let me get under this table.
Excuse me.
Got some high boots down there.
Stilettos at brunch. All right. girl.
Okay. okay.
It is getting hot in here.
No. no. no. no.
That was really fun.
Look. I don't get out much.
so this was fun for me.
Me neither.
You sure made their day.
They made my day. truly.
- This is my car.
- I mean. I've never been...
- This is you? Ooh. a Subaru.
- Yeah.
Yeah.
I like it.
All right. I'm-I'm getting my courage up.
Um...
I have two questions to ask you.
Two? Just two?
- Yeah.
- All right. Let's hear it.
Drumroll. Give me the first one. Go.
Um. you're gay. right?
- What? I'm what?
- You're gay.
- Gay? No.
- Yeah.
What?
- Are you kidding right now?
- No. I...
No. I mean. look. I don't have
anything against gays.
I love gays. but. like. I'm--
no. absolutely not.
- You just...
- What made you think I was gay?
You just seem like one of the girls.
Or. like. you seem to love women's shoes.
No. that's not what that was.
- All right.
- Uh-uh.
All right. well. that-- if that's a no.
we can go straight to question two.
Okay. Uh. yeah. I guess. hit me.
Um...
Um. would you like to go out with me?
On a date?
Okay.
Wow. you're a very forward person.
I. uh...
Um. yes. I would. I would very much--
really. very much--
like to go out on a date with you.
I don't know. yes.
Yes is the answer to that.
- All right.
- Okay.
I'm free. um. next Saturday morning?
Perfect.
I'll pick you up. Where do you live?
I live in a really boring. uh.
government building
that's non-disclosed to the public.
How about this?
Uh. let's meet at Freedom Park.
Saturday morning. 8:00 a.m.
Sounds like a. like a--
uh. well. sounds like a date.
- It's a date.
- So it's a date.
- Okay. Bye.
- All right. All right. Sorry.
- Hey.
You were shaking. and I was going...
But don't get... There's a car.
Oh. shit.
- Okay.
- All right. Yep.
- All right. that was awkward.
- Okay.
- See ya.
- Bye!
It's hot.
Wow.
You're in really good shape.
Thanks. girl.
- My ex. Jeffrey. he...
- Yeah?
- What?
- You said Jeffrey.
Yeah. That's my ex's name-- Jeffrey.
- Got it. right.
- Yeah.
His name was Jeffrey?
- Yeah. He was in...
- Wow.
...horrible shape.
Like. we had no...
- No...?
- It's just been a long time.
- Oh. okay.
- But we're nothing alike.
- Good to know.
- Yeah. I-I like people.
He didn't talk.
He just read war history novels
on the toilet.
What?
Mm-hmm.
N-No. Jeffrey. that is gross.
Right?
He loves his books.
but when it comes to time for the girls
or homework or driving lessons.
just doesn't show up.
Stressful.
I just think you need
a little bit more fun in your life.
to be honest.
Okay.
Do you want to go back to mine
and have some fun right now?
What?
- Really?
- Mm-hmm.
Yes. Very much. yes.
I would very much-- yeah. mm-hmm.
- Okay.
- Mm-hmm. Yeah. Now?
- Yeah.
- All right.
Told you I wasn't gay.
Shut up.
Tell me about your daughters.
Their names are Dee and Lindsay.
Dee's 11.
She's pretty sensitive and creative.
She's like... I don't know.
She-she hasn't let me cut her hair
since she was a baby.
She's one of those kids.
And then Lindsay's 16.
She has a sign on her door that says.
"Emotionally unavailable."
She also just got her learner's permit
but refuses to drive.
even though she wants her freedom.
- so that's where we're at.
- Oh. is that right?
Well. I'm a good driver.
If you want me to teach her.
I-I'll happily do it.
We just met.
That's a good point. That's a...
Yeah. I know.
Um. I just love kids. so...
Okay. well. maybe...
maybe you could meet 'em sometime.
You know. like. maybe
you could come over for...
for pizza one weekend. maybe?
Like a pizza party?
Can we have a pizza party?
Like a pizza Saturday?
I haven't been out of the house.
- let alone on a date. okay?
- Okay.
- In a very long time.
- Mm-hmm.
Um. I... I don't know if my girls
are ready for. you know.
M-Mom to be dating just yet.
I get that.
We can still have a pizza party
and just make it just totally normal.
I'm just a friend from church. you know.
that happens to be a government spy.
A non-gay one.
You know. a non-gay government spy
that just comes over
and wants to. you know.
have pizza with you and your daughters.
- You know. just make it normal.
- Okay.
You're-you're not normal. John.
but...
I like you.
- You know what's not normal?
- Hmm?
You just look like this all the time?
Looking inviting.
Oh.
He's here. Okay?
Hello.
Please come in.
Wow. that's a lot of food.
Girls. this is my friend John.
John. these are my girls.
Hey. girls.
Uh. hi. I'm-I'm John Zorin.
I'm your mom's good friend from church.
You must be Dee.
That's short for Delia?
- Yeah.
- Yes.
You must be Lindsay. and that's short for...
That's not short for anything
at all. actually.
Look. I've heard so much about you guys.
Uh. and one of the things
that I have heard.
is that you. Dee. happen to be
a huge fan of Zelda. like I am.
Is that true?
- Yeah.
- Is that right?
Good. 'cause I got you this Link doll.
And another question:
Have you played Four Swords?
- No.
- It is so amazing.
and it comes with this special controller
that I'll teach you how to use later
until you can whup my butt.
which you'll probably be able
to do really quickly
'cause I hear you're.
like. a Zelda master.
- Thanks.
- Yes. Zelda worked.
One down.
Lindsay. for you.
I have an assortment
of very angsty teenage music
for your listening pleasure.
Thank you?
No. thank you.
Nice to meet you. John Zorin.
Mom's friend from church.
- Where are you going?
- I have homework.
It's okay.
Maybe next time.
Okay?
All right? Don't worry.
I. uh. also happened
to have gotten you something.
- Miss Leigh.
- Oh.
This is all so sweet.
I'm sorry about Lindsay.
I-I thought this might be hard for her.
Yeah. No. and. look.
I understand that.
This one has to go on top.
Yeah. the top. top part.
And this one has to go...
But wait. where's the light...
Wait. you got to connect.
Oh. the click.
I love the click.
- And this one has to go on that.
- Dee?
Yeah.
It's 11 :00. Past 11 :00.
Oh. come on. let us finish this. Please?
Please? She's. like. the best builder.
We're like 20 pieces away from the end.
Yeah. please. Mom.
- So close.
- Another time. okay?
Okay.
- I had the best time with you. Okay?
- Yeah.
Can I see you again?
I'd like that.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
So. if it's late. I'll just come
and. like. tap on your window?
Oh.
I don't know if I'm a...
"tap on the window" kind of girl. John.
No?
All right. how about I just
knock on the front door?
Okay.
♪ I'll be home ♪
♪ When your nights are troubled ♪
♪ And you're all alone ♪
- ♪ Ooh ♪
- ♪ When you're feeling down ♪
- ♪ You need some sympathy♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ There's no one else around ♪
- ♪ Ooh ♪
- ♪ To keep you company♪
♪ Ooh ♪
- ♪ Ah ♪
- ♪ Remember. baby ♪
♪ You can always ♪
- ♪ Count on me ♪
♪ I'll be home ♪
♪ I'll be home. I'll be home ♪
♪ Wherever you may wander♪
♪ Wherever you may roam ♪
- ♪ Ooh ♪
- ♪ You come back♪
♪ I'll be waiting here for you ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
- ♪ Ah ♪
- ♪ I'll be here ♪
♪ To comfort you ♪
- ♪ And see you through ♪
♪ I'll be home. I'll be home ♪
- Goodbye. Halloween.
- ♪ I'll be home ♪
Turkey time.
- Don't hit the light.
- I won't.
Yeah. maybe next year
we should get an inflatable Otis.
Hey. I-I'm not stepping in this time.
Okay? You got to do it. You got to do it.
You got to punch the bully
in the nose. you know?
- My man. Otis.
- Yeah.
Yeah. I need to tell you something. Mitch.
- Whoa. okay.
- Yeah.
I mean-- okay. What?
Um...
What?
Uh...
Please say it.
-No. I'm sorry. Um. I'm just...
- What. what?
- Uh. I was. I was. um...
- Say it.
-Otis. come on.
- I...
Just say it.
-I wanted to tell you I-I...
- What?
I sweeped up the stockroom like you said.
-Okay. is that it?
- Yeah.
No. No.
My mom used to tell me
be careful what you touch.
She said that moving one grain of sand
changes everything in the whole universe.
I think people call it
the butterfly effect.
That just one butterfly
flapping its wings can
make a hurricane
on the other side of the world.
And before we know it. we're
banging into each other's paths
and changing what happens.
Are you sure you want bangs?
Sure.
It's a big change.
Thing is about bangs.
there's only about
one in a thousand people
that actually look good with bangs.
but good news is I think that
you might be one of them.
Oh. God.
No one notices the butterfly
flapping its wings
until everyone feels the storm.
I knew a storm was coming.
I knew if I stayed in one place too long.
eventually someone would recognize me.
I knew I had to leave.
I just didn't want to go alone.
You think you could
ever just move somewhere else?
Like a beach or something?
Start over in a new place?
I don't know. John.
I-I need to come back here. you know?
We could take the girls.
Just pack up and go.
Mm. That's...
No. I can't do that.
I can't do that.
My life is here. John.
♪ You're letting go ♪
♪ And if ttys real ♪
♪ Well. I don't want to know ♪
♪ Don't speak... ♪
♪ Stop explaining ♪
♪ Don't tell me
'Cause it hurts ♪
♪ Don't speak ♪
♪ I know what you're... ♪
♪ I don't need your reasons ♪
♪ Don't tell me
'Cause it hurts ♪
♪ Our memories ♪
♪ They can be inviting ♪
♪ But some erotically enticing ♪
♪ Writing ♪
♪ As we die ♪
♪ Both you and I... ♪
♪ Stop explaining ♪
♪ Don't tell me
'Cause it hurts ♪
♪ No. no. no. no. no ♪
What the fuck?
What? Oh. my God!
Oh. my God!
Oh. my God. there's a lot of you.
He's-he's big. He's naked! He came at me.
- Sir. is he still here?
- I don't know.
I heard the-the outer...
the alarm door went off.
So he may have gone outside?
- Uh. yes.
- Charlotte Police!
- Police department!
Police department!
The alarm was going off.
When we came back here. the door was ajar.
so we really believe he went out this way.
We could watch
the whole thing. Officer.
'cause I know how to... press
"play" on this thing. so...
- Mitch?
- Yeah?
The good news is
you have surveillance cameras
- all over the store.
- Yes. Yes.
Bad news...
is none of them were recording.
You need to fix that.
Now. besides the naked guy.
have you noticed anything strange
happening around here?
Uh. uh...
Uh. well. we're-we're missing
a lot of gaming inventory.
What's a lot?
A substantial amount.
You're gonna have to get
some real security in here. Mitch.
Workers at this Toys "R" Us
are prepping for the holiday rush.
but store manager Mitch Haggin says
he did not expect to see
what he saw this morning:
a strong. very tall. naked man.
Uh. a-a naked guy ran at me.
I think he was gonna kill me.
and I ran away.
locked myself in my office.
When I asked if the naked man
would scare off holiday shoppers.
Mr. Haggin said he was hiring
round-the-clock security.
We have a really good security
system here now. for sure.
Families can feel safe.
This is a safe place
to come for Christmas.
I think it looks great.
- Hi.
Hi.
We're almost ready to go.
Lord. we want to thank you
for this wonderful food.
and we want to thank you
for the gift of family. Amen.
Amen.
- Happy Thanksgiving.
Happy Thanksgiving.
- So. Leigh.
- Yes?
Why don't you tell us all
that story about the naked man.
Oh. it-it's nothing. y'all.
It... it was cold outside.
and a homeless man
needed to take a shower.
Yeah. but what if he's also a killer?
He's... Stop being over dramatic.
He's not a killer.
Your mom's totally right.
He's definitely not a killer.
You don't know that. John.
Well. if he was a killer.
he'd have killed him. right?
Uh. the paper said today that there
was $10.000 in video games stolen.
Mm.
I don't know
if that's a coincidence or not.
That is a lot of money.
Well. I don't know. Mom.
Maybe you should quit.
You have a master's degree.
and I don't think it's worth the risk.
It seems scary over there.
I mean. that's not
the worst idea. I guess.
- I like my job.
- Wait. Hold up.
Earlier. you just made it seem
like it wasn't dangerous.
So. if it's not dangerous. then-then why
does she have to quit so suddenly?
- Yeah.
- I don't know. I'm sorry.
Uh. did I. did I say she had to quit?
I don't think I did. actually.
I think I was just agreeing
with Lindsay down here.
I was just saying here that Lindsay
actually has a great idea.
If she wants to quit.
then she would have more time
with her girls.
- Yeah.
- Now. everybody.
let's not get too serious. because. uh...
I just think it's kind of funny.
I imagine the guy.
he's just going to work.
just a normal day.
and then he sees a naked guy
running around inside his toy store.
Makes me want
to get a job there. actually.
Oh. Kami. bless you.
Yeah. I just think
it's really funny. that's all.
I don't think it's funny. Ron.
I-I think it's sad.
I mean. someone's so desperate
they had to bathe in a toy store sink.
while we eat and laugh about it?
I mean. maybe we aren't Good Samaritans.
Mm.
Maybe you aren't
making the best decisions.
Excuse me. ma'am?
Choosing to work there
while Dee and I are home alone.
waiting for someone to pick us up
to take us places?
- Like. we...
- Whoa. whoa.
If we're being honest.
you're old enough to drive yourself.
I don't have a license.
I told you I would teach you. Okay?
I can't even
sit in the car with you.
And now that Dad's not here.
you bring around this weirdo.
and we're supposed to just accept it?
I-I hope the sex is worth it.
Hey. hey. hey.
Lin...
Sorry.
- Our church.
- Yeah.
Wow.
- Hello?
- Uh. hi.
Um. this is Cousin Oliver.
I was just calling for Steve.
It's 7:00 in the morning.
Uh. it's also December 1st.
and we had a conversation
a few months back
that I should call back on December 1st.
Yeah. you just call back. He's sleeping.
Okay. well. can you
just wake him up for me?
Um. just tell him it's Cousin Oliver.
All right? It's urgent.
- Baby.
- Mm. Mm.
It's your cousin. It's Cousin Oliver.
Tell him I'm asleep.
Motherfucker. Goddamn.
- He says...
- We can do it Sunday.
...he's asleep and that
you should come see him next Sunday.
Next Sunday. Okay. great.
Is he still in Fayetteville?
No. No. It's the Twin Pines Motel.
Twin Pines. Okay.
Room 204.
- 204. I got it.
- And don't be
a fucking dumb-ass and take the bus.
He says don't be a fucking dumb-ass
and take the bus.
He wants to know if you got a car.
Yep. Tell the sarge.
uh. I'll take care of that
and I'll see him on Sunday as scheduled.
H-Hi. Morning.
You didn't tell me you had to take a trip.
You weren't supposed to hear that.
Okay.
Look. it's not a big deal.
I just have to go and just check in.
- That's all.
- Okay.
Mwah.
Morning. Lindsay.
Good morning. Leigh. Good morning. Dee.
Everybody want to say "good morning"?
Morning. John.
All right. who wants
to apologize first. hmm?
No? You?
Come on. guys.
Nobody has anything to say to each other?
Look. families fight.
That's fine. but they also make up.
Come on.
I'm sorry for the way
I've been acting. Lindsay.
Great work.
I shouldn't have said the thing about sex
in front of Dee.
Mm. Yeah.
And...
And? You got it.
And I need a ride to Doug's.
Nope. That wasn't...
You aren't getting a ride anywhere.
Do you have any idea how much
you embarrassed me last night?
I embarrassed you?
John. will you drive me?
You do not get to abuse him
and then ask him for favors.
It's okay.
I-I don't mind driving her.
- No. stay out of this. John.
- See. he doesn't mind.
If she wants to go somewhere.
she can learn to drive.
I'm not driving in that car
with that stick shift with you ever.
Well. then I guess
you'll never go anywhere again!
- Okay. time-out. Time-out.
- Ever!
I'm sorry. can I ask my mom
to drive me places
- 'cause she's my mother?
- Okay. stop.
I have an idea. okay?
I have an idea. Hear me out.
It's a great idea.
We need a beater.
What even is a beater. John?
♪ Come. they told me ♪
♪ Pa. rum. pum. pum. pum... ♪
That's a nice ride
right there. huh?
Classic 1999 with very low mileage.
- Yeah?
- Great color. too.
Awesome family car.
It's automatic.
It is automatic. Great price.
- You guys want to try it out?
- Yeah.
- Got the keys right here.
- Look at that.
It's nice seats. right?
You know. modern cars
just don't have the same feel.
This is kind of like the golden era.
The '90s.
You know. just... They don't make
modern cars like this anymore. you know?
- Yeah.
- These-these are like sofas.
- You guys buckled up?
- Yeah. yeah.
- Any cops around here ever?
- Oh. no. no.
Nobody's gonna stop you here.
Just gonna push it just a little bit.
Okay.
Oh. oh. oh. oh.
It's got some horsepower. Okay.
All right. all right.
Got a nice V-6...
Okay. Okay.
Hey. hey. hey. hey!
Hey. sir! Sir!
- Watch out!
- Here we go.
Oh. Oh! Oh!
Fuck!
Fuck! Slow down! Slow down!
Slow down! Slow down! It's a used car!
Slow down!
Slow down! Slow down!
♪ I played my best for him ♪
♪ Pa. rum. pum. pum. pum... ♪
You guys okay?
- Motherfucker!
- Yeah?
All right. good.
What's wrong with you. man?
- Calm down.
- No. no. get out.
- Calm down. No. no. no.
- Get out. Get out!
- I'm driving us back.
- Lindsay. Lindsay. Stop.
Calm down. Lindsay. get up here.
You drive. You in the back.
No. maybe she shouldn't drive. John.
No. No. she's a kid! She can't drive!
- It's busy here. It's busy.
- No. she can drive. Listen.
- No. give me the keys right now.
- No. no.
Stop. stop. Calm down. okay?
How do you teach a kid to swim?
You throw them in the water.
Right? If you want her to drive.
- we got to let her drive.
- Oh. yeah. Go. Lindsay.
Does she even have a license?
- She has her permit.
- No.
No. you cannot
test-drive with a permit.
Look. listen. I'm gonna purchase this car
if the young lady approves.
and I'm gonna pay cash.
How's that sound to you?
I'll let you hold it.
Come on.
Yes.
Get up here. You're driving.
All right.
Seat belts. Safety first.
All right. this is not
a manual transmission.
This is an automatic.
so it's so much easier.
You can just forget about your left foot.
It's all right foot.
So put your right foot
on that brake right there.
the big pedal.
Yep. push it all the way in.
All the way in. Real firm.
Okay. now you're gonna
take your right hand.
you're gonna pull that
towards you and down to "D."
Perfect. Now let it go.
Back at two.
All right. We're not
gonna worry about the gas.
You're just gonna ease
your foot off the brake
and we're just gonna move forward.
and that's it.
All right? Take a big breath.
You got this.
You got it. Come on.
You got it. Go. go. go. go. go.
Yeah. yeah. yeah. yeah. That's good.
- Nice.
- Good one.
All right. family.
I always love to take pictures
of my happy customers.
if you guys don't mind.
All right.
Big smile.
One more. one more.
Now. let's pretend your dad
almost crashed the car.
All right.
Hey. great. great stuff. guys.
Thank you very much.
You're a better driver than him.
That's true. actually. I felt really.
really safe with you. so good job.
Oh. I'm glad.
- Thank you. John.
- Congrats. man.
Will you girls wait in the car
while I talk to John
for just. like. a minute? Here.
Okay.
We got a beater.
Yeah. we got a beater. Yeah.
I have to say it.
- I did not like that driving.
- Okay.
I'm sorry. I know.
I shouldn't have done that.
Yeah.
But Lindsay was a really.
really good first-time driver.
Wasn't she? She was great.
- Yeah.
- She did so good.
And-and-- I don't know--
I think she's starting to like me.
They both like you.
They really like you. okay?
I like you.
Just... just need to slow it
down a little bit. okay?
Okay.
And we don't need so many things. John.
We just want you.
Just be you. Be normal.
- I promise. The most normal.
- Okay.
You take your trip.
and when you come back.
we'll have a-a few normal nights. okay?
No more stunt driving. I promise.
Okay.
Oh. gosh.
- I love John.
- Oh. my God.
The car. I love the car.
- It's the perfect car.
- See you back at the house.
Okay.
- Hi.
Uh. Cousin Oliver.
- Here for Steve.
- Oh. Mm. it's a little early.
- Hey. Steve?
- Yeah?
Cousin Oliver's here.
Hello. dumb dog.
Yeah. I knew you'd show up
at the crack of dawn
if I ain't give you a time.
- Welcome home. Sarge.
- Man.
- All right. you...
- Oh. man.
Yeah. that is enough. Yeah.
Damn. you look clean
for a motherfucker that's on the run.
I'm trying. I'm trying.
- Where you was hiding out at. church?
- You know I can't tell you that.
Seriously. where you hiding out at?
No. I can't tell you that.
You don't want to know that.
You ain't got no contact. right?
- You ain't talking to nobody?
- No. no.
Okay. 'cause you know if you are.
I can't help you.
No. why would I do that?
- You good?
- I'm good. I'm good.
Keep your eyes on me. then.
Why you keep darting them around?
I'm not darting them.
I'm looking right at you.
- You sure you're all right?
- Look.
Okay.
We gonna need to change that hair
before we take the photo.
Uh. baby. what you think? Wig? Dye?
For-for his hair.
I think we do a wig.
Yeah. Don't worry. Jeff.
You'll still be you.
But cuter. Like Brad Pitt.
Ugly-ass Brad Pitt.
Oh. my God.
Baby. are you serious about this?
I'm-I'm...
This is a panty dropper.
Oh. my God. Baby. come on.
Okay.
Oh.
You got to be fucking kidding me. baby.
Say hi. baby.
Wow.
Baby. th-that's... that's a good one.
- That's good. right?
- Yeah.
- This one feel good to you?
- Mm-hmm.
Mm-hmm? Feels like you could be
- this person for a while?
- Mm-hmm.
- You ready?
Wait. wait. wait. wait.
Stop with the damn smiling.
Fuck you doing?
- Just... normal face.
- No. yeah. serious.
It's like a... it's your passport. you know.
You're not allowed to smile.
One. two. three.
Read this shit. Study it.
All of it.
All right? It's gonna be the new you.
You're Kenneth Owen Griffin.
Born July 7. 1974.
from Lumberton. North Carolina.
Now. I'm-a get all your documents.
Don't worry about shit.
Transfers. records--
I'll have it all done. A to Z.
Okay. What-what are you thinking. like 5K?
Oh. no. it's gonna be
a lot more than that. man.
More than that? How-how much more?
You think I don't know
what you doing. huh?
You probably got a girlfriend. don't you?
What? No.
Yeah. you do. Yeah. you do.
Yeah. you not good at this shit.
- Good at what shit?
- Being a criminal. nigga.
Let me tell you something.
Good criminals are cold. calculating.
You understand?
Now. you got the calculation down.
but. man. you just... goofy.
The price... it's gonna be 50K.
All right?
- 50? 50?
- Yeah.
Hey. you a lot of risk. man.
Can you do it?
Okay. Yeah.
How you gonna do it?
I'll get it. I'll get it.
Well. if you're thinking about
using a gun. do me a favor.
Stay the fuck off the TV.
Roof man. you understand what I'm saying?
Don't do anything stupid.
Ow.
Okay.
Shit.
What the...?
Shit!
Stupid idiot!
90% of our annual sales
happens in the next two weeks.
Think about that.
There's gonna be a lot of money coming in.
and we need to be ready for it.
Considering our recent setbacks.
I think we're doing pretty good.
You should be proud. Come on.
Come on. guys. Come on. Come on.
But the ball game starts now.
We're beefing up security
so the store is safe
and families feel safe in the store.
Right on schedule.
Because if our customers
have a good Christmas.
then so do we.
You are so punctual. my friend. I like it.
Your job is to sell toys.
It's gonna be a little bit
heavier this time around.
Yeah. getting a lot of these lately.
It's good for your arms. muscles there.
We're gonna open early
and stay open late every day
this Christmas season.
and that includes Christmas Eve.
I posted the new schedule.
Now. I know some of you
are gonna have shifts they don't want.
but there's no exceptions or changes.
You show up when your name
is on the schedule.
Now. let's have a happy Christmas.
Let's do this for the kids.
Come on. Back to work.
♪ Oh. our Father is the maker of Mary ♪
♪ And Mary is the mother of his Son ♪
♪ The Son is a blessing from the Father♪
♪ So let's hear thanks and praise ♪
♪ Sing happy Christmas ♪
♪ To you ♪
♪ You... ♪
Nice hat.
You look like a Christmas supervillain.
Yeah. I am a Christmas supervillain.
You're driving. though.
- I'm driving?
- You are driving.
Okay.
Holy shit. you got so much stuff.
Mom's gonna freak out.
Yeah. she's gonna freak out with joy.
♪ Coming back for everyone ♪
♪ Christmas is coming back again... ♪
- Hi. Mom.
Okay.
Perfect timing.
Everyone's ready to go.
Mwah.
Hey. guys.
- I can't go to church tonight.
- Why not?
I have to wake up super early.
I have a shift tomorrow.
Then I have good news for you.
Mitch called. and he's gonna be a nice guy
and let you sleep in.
- Mitch called?
- Mm-hmm. Yeah.
Uh. said 10:30.
- 10:30?
- Yeah.
10:30 to 4:30. I think he said.
Why?
I. uh... I don't know.
I mean. maybe he knows
that you have a family
and he wants you to be able
to spend the holidays with them.
♪ Coming back for everyone... ♪
Mm-hmm.
- Hey. Mom.
- Hey.
- I love you.
I love you.
Come on into the manger.
♪ Well. she said there was no room ♪
- ♪ No room ♪
♪ No room at the inn ♪
♪ Well. well. the time had fully come ♪
♪ For the Savior to be born ♪
♪ But they told her there was no room ♪
- ♪ No room ♪
♪ No room at the inn ♪
♪ Hey. hey. hey♪
- ♪ According to the Word ♪
- ♪ Oh. yes ♪
♪ There was a virgin girl ♪
- ♪ Hey. hey♪
- ♪ Oh. yes ♪
- ♪ Mother of Jesus ♪
- ♪ Wandering round that night ♪
- ♪ Oh. yes ♪
♪ She was trying to find a place ♪
♪ For the Savior to be born ♪
♪ But they told her there was no room ♪
- ♪ No room ♪
♪ No room at the inn ♪
♪ I said there was no room ♪
- ♪ No room ♪
♪ No room at the inn ♪
♪ One more time
There was no room ♪
- ♪ No room ♪
♪ No room at the inn ♪
♪ I said the time had fully come ♪
♪ For the Savior to be born... ♪
Otis. back to work. Come on.
Clean that nursery. would you?
- Like I told you to.
- Okay.
- Hello. sir.
- Hello.
Mr. Money Man. Mr. Money Man.
♪ Just hear those sleigh bells jingling... ♪
Good morning.
Toys "R" Us employees!
Hello. This is the police.
You guys. you know you got an alarm
going off back there?
Everybody. this way.
You're coming with me. Little faster.
Oh. my God.
Oh. my God. He has a gun.
Hey. hey. hey. hey. hey!
Please keep your hand away
from your gun. sir.
Get on. get on your stomach.
You two. come here.
No one's gonna get hurt
if everybody just does what I say.
On your stomach. Otis. here.
Zip-tie everybody up.
- Otis. come on.
- Uh...
Jesus Christ. Mitch. zip-tie everybody up.
Okay? Get on your stomachs. eyes down.
- Okay.
- Wh-What did I say?
Come on. On your stomach.
Get down.
Don't do this right now.
Hey. hey.
What did I say?
Shit.
That wasn't my fault.
He's a bad listener.
This is not happening.
Everybody. take a breath.
Mitch. give me one of those.
Thank you. sir.
Sorry. Sorry.
Okay.
- Sorry. Sorry.
- Come on. Mitch.
Let's get a hop on. Let's go.
It's gonna be okay. Sorry. Sorry.
Guys.
Everybody. just calm down.
I'm sorry about this.
Mitch. get the keys. Come on.
- Let's go to the safe.
- No. there's no money here.
- There's no safe.
- You think I don't know
that there's a deposit that you
take to the bank every Tuesday?
Huh? Come on. please.
You're okay.
Eyes down. Eyes down.
I'm sorry about this. guys.
It'll be all over in a second.
Come on. You do this every day. Calm down.
Come on. Here we go. Good job.
Eyes down.
Just... find the key.
Oh. God.
Eyes down out there!
Yes. Okay. put it in.
- Oh. Okay.
- Put it in the safe and open it.
Take the bag out. Put it down.
I need you to take the ink bomb out.
If I do that. it'll blow up everywhere.
Not if you do it quick.
Zip it right back up really fast. okay?
Okay.
Okay. good.
Oh. God.
Goddamn it.
He needs an ambulance!
You said you weren't gonna hurt anyone.
but you hurt him!
He needs an ambulance!
And you're just a bully!
You're just a bully!
Otis?
♪ O come. all ye faithful ♪
I can't see.
He need...
he needs an ambulance.
♪ Joyful and triumphant... ♪
I guess it's obvious
I'm just a pushover. huh?
All right. Otis.
Fine. I'm calling 911. okay?
♪ To Bethlehem ♪
♪ Come and behold him ♪
911. What's your emergency?
♪ Born the king of angels ♪
♪ O come. let us ♪
- ♪ Adore him ♪
- Shit.
♪ O come. let us adore him ♪
- ♪ O come. let us ♪
- Shit!
♪ Adore him ♪
♪ Christ the Lord ♪
♪ Sing... ♪
- Charlotte Police!
Police department!
♪ Sing in exultation ♪
Oh. oh. wow. Okay. Wait a second.
♪ Sing. all ye citizens... ♪
You were calling him names.
He had a gun.
and he was calling him a bully.
Oh. man.
♪ Glory to God ♪
♪ In the highest. glory ♪
♪ O come. let us adore him... ♪
Did you see any part of his skin
or any other clothing?
Um. I could tell
he was a white man. yeah.
Did you see his eyes?
Mm-mm.
This is fucking fantastic. Jeff.
You a fucking nut. you know that?
It's fucking great. Baby. you see this?
Yeah.
Okay. let's see.
This is your North Carolina-issued
driver's license. all right?
That's your passport.
Notarized birth certificate.
You got your check stubs
from your last job.
Oh. and there is your ticket.
You leave at 11 :00 p.m. out of Charlotte.
Now. what you're gonna do
is a layover in Miami.
and then you're gonna fly to Barranquilla.
From there. you're gonna take a little bus
and it'll have you in Venezuela
before the weekend's out.
Looks like I got everything I need
in case I decide to go tomorrow.
"Decide"?
You already made your decision. man.
What you talking about?
I mean. you can't expect me
to go on Christmas. right?
Can't I just stay awhile?
I'll just lay low.
That's not a choice you have. Jeff.
You got to leave tomorrow.
I got people waiting on you. man.
I got a security guy in Miami.
He'll be at line three.
- You got one shot. man.
- 00 p.m. tomorrow.
Don't miss this shot. All right?
Baby. let's get this. uh. wig on him.
You bet.
One more thing I was thinking about.
Saw on the TV there was some shit
about a armed robbery.
I don't know nothing about that.
I need your thumbs.
You know. you got
to cover your tracks. Jeff.
- Yeah.
- Everything you touch.
I need you to really think
about who you talked to.
who talked to you. who knows your voice.
I'm over a cliff for you. man.
You understand that. right?
Yeah.
So. nothing?
No doctor's visits?
Uh. I went to the dentist
and got some cavities filled.
But that's it.
Okay. You ain't get no X-rays?
No. I got X-rays.
but I gave 'em a fake name.
Okay. Well. it don't really matter
if you gave 'em a fake name
if they got your teeth. Jeff.
All right. Yeah.
Look. I'll take care of it.
Any messes you made. you clean it up.
Then you go straight to the airport
and wait for your flight.
No getting on the news.
No good-byes to anyone you said hello to.
That means no postcards. no calls.
No none of that.
Shit. we had a good run.
You know?
You know. after all this stuff
calms down and. like.
I get settled over there.
do you think you could tell
some people where I'm at
and they maybe could... visit me sometime?
No. no. no.
It's none of that. man.
Nobody coming to see you. Jeff.
You're starting over.
You're on your own now.
Yeah.
Oops.
Hello?
John.
I was just about to call you.
Is everything okay?
I've been calling you.
Where are you?
I'm driving.
Well. actually. I just pulled over.
Are you coming to Christmas dinner?
The girls have been asking for you.
Yeah. Yeah. of course.
Yeah. I wouldn't miss it.
Want to meet us at 5:00?
At home?
At 5:00? Yeah. yeah. that sounds good.
Yeah. I'll be there.
You there? Are you okay?
I can hear you. I can hear you breathing.
I love you. John.
I love you. too. Leigh.
I'll see you at 5:00.
Leigh?
Merry Christmas--
Police! Lay down!
- Get on the ground!
- Get down!
Get on the ground! Get on the ground!
- On the ground! Get down.
- Get down.
Don't move.
- Don't move.
- Do not move.
Doing good. Don't move.
Do as we say and you won't get hurt.
You understand me?
I got him. Nuh-uh.
Don't move. dickhead.
- Don't fucking move.
- Drama's over.
What's your name?
I think you know my name.
Jeffrey Manchester.
- PID. Target.
- We got him.
We got the Roof man.
He almost made it.
Let's move.
Come on.
Search his ass.
He's a tricky motherfucker.
This way. Come here.
Search him good.
I probably let myself get caught.
Or maybe I just couldn't leave
without saying goodbye.
They threw the book at me.
Gave me 384 more months.
That means by the time I get out of here.
I'll be an old man.
Gave me a lot of time
to think about my life.
Everything.
When I was out there in the world.
I wasn't thinking of the things
or people that I was putting at risk.
Now that's all I think about.
We all like to go back in time to imagine
how things could've gone differently
if we made different choices.
Like right now.
I was imagining what it would've been like
if I never committed all those crimes
and lost my family.
Or if I got to keep on living
with Leigh and her girls forever.
Sure. they'd boss me around a little
and make me go to church.
But they'd laugh at my dumb jokes
and forgive me
when I was on the wrong part
of cold and calculating.
Or something.
I started to realize
that all those people I loved
didn't need me
to give them so many things.
They just needed me.
My time.
And now that's all I have.
- Time.
- I got four A's.
You got all A's?
Yeah.
- Even in math?
- Yeah.
Becky. I'm so proud of you.
It all could've gone
a different way. for sure.
But it didn't. It went this way.
Hey. buddy.
And that was okay with me.
'Cause in here. I...
I can't hurt anybody anymore.
Yeah. I'm...
I'm where I'm supposed to be.
You ever think about it?
What?
You know.
breaking out of this place.
- No. No.
- Mm.
I'm...
This is my home now.
You know.
I have to admit. brother. like.
that love story part was really good.
I am curious. You ever see Leigh again?
- Hey.
- Hi.
Should I call you Jeffrey?
Just another jerk Jeffrey
in your life. I guess. Yeah.
How's Lindsay and Dee?
They're okay.
Yeah.
Did Dee keep her bangs?
She did.
Yeah.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry that I hurt you.
I'm sorry I couldn't protect you.
You don't have anything
to be sorry about. Leigh.
You don't.
You didn't hurt anybody.
You just told the truth.
Yeah.
I was really angry at you.
I was most angry
at how you hurt the girls.
But that's not the way
I think about it now.
Okay?
I think about it as an adventure.
We had a lot of fun.
We're thankful.
Well...
Maybe I'll come visit you sometime.
Gonna tap on my window?
Maybe I'll just knock on the door.
The Roof man
has returned to rob again.
over night cutting his way
into this McDonald's
on the intersection of Wilkinson and Main.
Just to look at what he's done.
it appears he's very intelligent.
Um. it's just that
he also likes to commit crime.
Holes cut into the roofs.
workers told to get into the coolers.
but no one was hurt.
In fact. the suspect was nice.
Very polite person.
He always makes sure that the employees.
be tore he walked them
into the refrigerator.
that he has them put on their coats
so that they'll stay warm.
This was an earlier.
composite drawing of Roof man.
always wearing a mask.
The owner here refused to comment
on all details of the robbery.
referring calls to
the McDonald's corporation.
But he's also robbed
Burger King and Blockbuster...
Police caught him
with $9.000 in cash.
allegedly stolen from
two McDonald's restaurants.
the first in Gastonia.
the second in Belmont.
The suspect a!most got away.
until a worker at this Belmont McDonald's
saw which way he ran
and then called police.
I interacted with Jeffrey on the robbery
that happened
in the McDonald's in Belmont.
The whole time. he was saying.
"I'm so sorry.
You guys are the good people.
I'm the bad person."
He was a nice fella.
He. uh. he was real nice.
He didn't. uh...
he didn't come across as. uh...
you know. come up. talk junk. you know.
Or. "Why am I here?" Nothing like that.
You know. he... he was a nice fella.
He's an incredible liar.
um. pretty much about everything.
Everybody thinks. "Oh. he's such a hero
"because he-he gave the toys
to the children."
Well. the toys are stolen.
As far as. like. having an inkling
to maybe there's something there.
no. I didn't have any kind of inkling.
He was a nice tell a.
He got involved in our church.
But now that the pastor. knows
John is really Jeffrey Manchester.
the escaped convict accused
of sticking up Toys "R" Us
and torching a dentist's is office.
how does he feel?
My belief is that. um.
as a church.
you got to stand with somebody.
Doesn't mean that you agree
with what they did.
The Rootman. or the Rooftop Robber.
I-I never heard anything about that.
It was-- I was oblivious to anything
until after my relationship with Jeffrey.
and then he was captured.
Then it just seemed to be everywhere.
Never thought that
would happen to my office.
him trying to burn it down
to-to hide his record.
The whole front area was gone.
In the beginning. it just seemed to me
he had everything together.
And it's a perfect example
of how greed and money
and bad influences in your lite
could change your outcome.
pastor. Smith says
he's already visited Manchester in jail.
He could not believe
that I came to see him.
that. um. that we would
not just be really mad at him
and turn our back on him.
A!though it was
a church member who turned Manchester in.
Police captured him
leaving the apartment of Leigh Wainscott.
the new girlfriend he met
at a church singles event.
I talked to my oldest daughter.
you know. about this.
um. recently. and. uh. I asked her
to share with me
anything that she remembered.
um. that she could share.
and she just said.
"Oh. yeah. I remember very well.
He was. he was awesome. you know.
We had so much fun."
And. um...
They didn't have anything bad
to say about him.
Nothing at all.